Eduard Gabriel Arghir

Email address: arghir.eduard@yahoo.com in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/eduard-arghir/

ABOUT ME

Software Engineer with a passion for exploring new technologies within different sectors. I have a strong foundation in software engineering and programming skills, with an innate ability to learn and master new technologies.

I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated, reliable, responsible and hard working person. I am a mature team worker and adaptable to all challenging situations.

I have good knowledge and experience using Python, Javascript, React and other technologies like Git, Jira and many more.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Test Automation Engineer

Luxoft Romania [05/2023 - Current]

City: Bucharest | Country: Romania

- · Automated testing Python Scania project
- Working with CANoe and VCI on a testing RIG and replicating the sensors received by the truck to make sure they work correctly
- Working in the same team with developers from Backend, Frontend, C# and testing whatever they are implementing
- Implementing an Automated Test Suite in Python using Pytest, Selenium
- · Working with Jira, Git, Gitlab

Test Automation Engineer

Bertrandt Romania [02/2023 - 04/2023]

City: Bucharest | Country: Romania

- Software testing CARIAD project
- Writing tests in Python for codes written in Java: receiving multiple Java codes every 4 weeks and writing Python tests for each Java code to test multiple cases
- Using NDS (Navigation Data Standard) database
- · Working with Jira, Git, Bitbucket

Software Engineer

Bertrandt Romania [02/2022 - 01/2023]

City: Bucharest | Country: Romania

- Software Development Renault project
- Developing new tools for a multitude of automotive applications: using Python, OOP, different Python libraries like Pandas and Numpy, Selenium framework, building GUIs
- Testing the functionality of written classes/functions/scripts
- Maintaining and enhancing existing tools: debugging errors that occur in different tools either in Matlab or in Python, improving existing tools by adding features and making the code more readable and faster
- Participated in code reviews
- · Working within an Agile team, attached to a Product Owner: receiving tasks from the end-users, working with Jira

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Engineering - Transport and Traffic Engineering

University POLITEHNICA of Bucharest [2017 – 2021]

City: Bucharest | Country: Romania

High School Degree - Mathematics - Informatics

National College "Nicolae Grigorescu" [2013 – 2017]

City: Campina | Country: Romania

CERTIFICATIONS

[02/2024 - 07/2024]

Front-end Web Development

I finished a 5 months paid course about Front-end development by ITSchool. Here I learned HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript and React. At the end I took an exam and received a diploma accredited by the ministry.

[03/2024]

PCAP - Certified Associate in Python Programming

[11/2023]

PCEP - Certified Entry-Level Python Programmer

[07/2022]

Udemy - 100 Days of Code: The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp

Link: ude.my/UC-ff769d6a-116e-43b9-aae3-8f46e90200f9